[Music] The
event that took place today, Nita Desai Traffic
DCP West Ahmedabad City, the special purpose of the traffic
awareness program
organized by ICICI Lombard was
that school children should get an understanding of
wearing helmets on two-wheelers from now on.
Their parents have also been
kept with them, so helmets have also been
distributed to them, so a message has been given that children and
parents should wear helmets whenever they go on two-wheelers.
If this understanding is given to children from now on, then surely
whenever their parents drive two-wheelers in their homes, the
children themselves will
let them wear helmets that you should drive two-wheelers only after wearing a helmet.
This is a
matter of developing a sense of traffic from now on. This is a
really good effort from ICICI Lombard
and our Ahmedabad City Traffic also
applauds their efforts.
Ahmedabad City Traffic is being supported in this helmet distribution
program by ICICI Lombard.  Thanks to the help and traffic
awareness organized in this program,
traffic awareness will really
develop among the children. Jai Hind Jai Bharat
I will give it to you
[Music]
Media
Party Media